

Uroš Glogovac

Final year student at The School of Electrical and Computing Engineer of **Applied Studies**

glogovacu@gmail.com

+381621620999



Smederevo, Serbia



Experienced in C#, .NET, Unity, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL and Android development. Currently, I am focused on enhancing my OOP abilities by creating Unity games, refining my frontend skills through the development of my Portfolio website, expanding my Android expertise by working on a Weather App and improving my .NET knowledge by refactoring my Hotel Management application.

EDUCATION

Technical School Smederevo

09/2016 - 06/2020

Courses

Computer Network Administrator

School of Electrical and Computer **Engineering of Applied Studies** Belgrade

10/2020 - Present

Courses

New Computer Technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Worker

Fruvita

07/2022 - 08/2022

Kolari,Smederevo

Unity Developer deCode GmbH

02/2023 - Present

Remote Indie game company for a game called "The Simple Balance"

SKILLS



PROJECTS

https://glogovacu.github.io/Portfolio/

 My portfolio page made with HTML, CSS and JavaScript. The page showcases my skills and projects in a dynamic and engaging manner.

https://github.com/glogovacu/textAplikacija

C# Windows Forms Application that works with text files (.txt). Provides seamless functionality and efficient management of hotel-related data.

https://glogovacu.github.io/First-Person-Shooter/

First Person Shooter game made with Unity. The game features enemy zombies, a gun system and an upgrade system.

https://github.com/glogovacu/WeatherApp

 Android weather application that utilizes an API key to retrieve and display accurate weather information.

LANGUAGES

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

